<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
 <title>moonpunter("techlog")</title>
 <description>notes and logs by P. H. Madore</description>
 <link>http://moonpunter.xyz</link>
 
  <item>
  <title>1485197768</title>
        <description>Most of my life, I didn&rsquo;t work for myself, or set my own schedule. Most of my life, I did crap that I didn&rsquo;t want to do for a living. When I finally got the chance to work for myself, I jumped at it. All those years I had spent cramming hackathons into my weekends – I would be great. And at first, I was. But then, you develop habits. You get on Facebook too long, etc. There are a lot of things you can do to alleviate the distraction portion of life, but the thing I&rsquo;ve done to ensure that I get back on task fast is to create a little script that pops open my new &ldquo;primary_work&rdquo; folder. That&rsquo;s all it does. That&rsquo;s all it has to do. The whole thing is right here: (continued)</description>
        <link>http://moonpunter.xyz/2017/1485197768.html</link>
        <pubDate>Mon Jan 23 2017 12:56:08 UTC-0600 (CST)</pubDate>
 </item>
 
 <item>
  <title>1484234668</title>
        <description>You have to resist the urge to repackage everything you love and make those two or three changes. It&rsquo;s not what you're trying to do. Everyone would like to go back and take credit for everything from the beginning of computing until now, but it's just now how it works.</description>
        <link>http://moonpunter.xyz/2017/1484234668.html</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 
  <item>
   <title>1457990934</title>
   <description>Often, things will not go as planned. The core measure of your might is how long you're willing to continue prodding in the same direction, despite it all, hoping to get what you came for.</description>
   <link>http://moonpunter.xyz/2016/1457990934.html</link>
   <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 21:28:54 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
   
   
   <item>
   <title>1457877574</title>
   <description>There's a lot of value in being able to go over the existing code in complete. Sometimes, it's worth the time to invest just to go over the entire codebase you already have in front of you, rather than jumping around searching for specific things.</description>
   <link>http://moonpunter.xyz/2016/1457877574.html</link>
   <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 13:59:34 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  
  <item>
   <title>1457440198</title>
   <description>Python CGI "Premature End of Script Header" Apache 2 Error: A Checklist :: The first thing you need to try is just running a script in general. This will knock out the general errors that might be encountered when trying to use Python as CGI. So here you are...</description>
   <link>http://moonpunter.xyz/2016/1457440198.html</link>
   <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 13:48:47 +0000</pubDate>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <title>1456864312</title>
  <description>If the purpose of tool kits is to make developing UIs easier, then they should be less complex, I think. As much as I love spending half the day <code>RTFM</code>'ing, it seems even the most basic concepts have become overcomplicated by perhaps lack of focus. Let's hope that future renditions of Qt and GTK manage to unify things in such a way that new methods are interoperable with old ones, such that an old method will be automatically detected at compile time, and then the compiler informs you of how the exact same thing would look in the new version. Then you just update those lines, and you're still not spending the day learning multiple things to accomplish one basic task.</description>
  <link>http://moonpunter.xyz/2016/1456864312.html</link>
  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 20:31:52 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 
 
 <item>
  <title>1456587276</title>
  <description>Part of me feels like the computer should be doing all this for me. Google's Photos app can know when it's Christmas, the computer should therefore almost be to the point where it does what I mean.</description>
  <link>http://moonpunter.xyz/2016/1456587276.html</link>
  <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 15:34:36 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>
 
 <item>
  <title>1456466149</title>
  <description>And why are you so stuck on continuing the zombie of Python 2.7 anyways?</description>
  <link>http://moonpunter.xyz/2016/1456466149.html</link>
  <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 07:14:43 +0000</pubDate>
 </item>

</channel>
</rss>